Is something happening?
何か起こしてる?
Shall I cry?
泣いてあげる?
Are you crying?
泣いてる?
It's so wet.
ビチャビチャだ
This posture.
この姿勢
I was so wet in this position.
この姿勢でビチャビチャだった
happiness?
幸せ?
Happy people are tied up.
幸せ者がつさがれて
Kun-chan, I'm starting to get excited.
くんちゃん、デラブになってきた
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I've endured eye strain.
アイエキ耐えてきたよ
This eye strain is amazing,
このアイエキがすごくてさ、
It's amazing.
すごい 出てる
You like this, right?
これ好きでしょ?
this.
これ
It looks like he was holding it down with his legs closed.
足閉じて押さえてたらしい
Strong breeding?
飼育強い?
Breeding is strong.
飼育強いよ
That's about it.
このくらいだな
Yeah.
うん
It's like after the licking lottery passes.
舐めくじが通った後みたい
here.
ここ
After the licking lottery passes.
舐めくじが通った後です
amazing.
すごい
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
Which one feels better?
どっちが気が気持ちいい?
This one or this one.
こっちか、これ
This way?
こっち?
this.
これ
Strong breeding.
飼育強い
amazing.
すごい
A face that looks like it's going to break out.
きれそうな顔
Can you go?
いけんの?
What are you doing?
なにやってんの?
Tsukumi.
つくみ
strange?
おかしい?
This one.
こっちが
I'll bring the gold balls.
金玉持ってくるよ
What are you eating?
何食べてるの?
Chinjin.
ちんじん
What do you do?
何する?
Do you think we'll get along?
仲良いすると思う?
Eh, are you going to put it in?
えー、入れちゃうの?
It feels good even if it's slow, yeah
ゆっくりでも気持ちいいよ うん、
Do you like both Do you like both?
どっちも好き どっちも好き?
Ah, it feels good
あー、気持ちいい
Take it out
出 して